<resources>

    <!--Application Title -->
    <string name="app_name">Static Recall App</string>

    <!--Screen Titles -->
    <string name="title_content">Static Recall</string>
    <string name="title_activity_store_location">Store Location</string>
    <string name="title_activity_listview_search">Search Stored Items</string>
    <string name="title_activity_search_location_screen">Item Location Information</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_screen">About Screen Activity</string>

    <!--Button Strings -->
    <string name="search_button">Find It</string>
    <string name="store_button">Stash It</string>
    <string name="edit_button">Edit</string>
    <string name="about_button">About</string>

    <!--Searchbar Strings -->
    <string name="searchbar">Search for...</string>
    <string name="search_items">Search for Item</string>

    <!--List View and Expandable List View Strings -->
    <string-array name="category_list">
        <item>Uncategorized</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="category_view">View Categories</string>
    <string name="search_title">Item Location Information</string>
    <string name="search_hint">Search stored items</string>
    <string name="view_categories">View Categories</string>
    <string name="view_items">View Items</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!--About Screen Strings -->
    <string name="welcome_message">Welcome to Static Recall</string>
    <string name="welcome_about_info">The finder app to ease your stress when you need to locate an
        item used at infrequent intervals - tell the app where you’ve put important documents, your
        passport, medications or perhaps even that sweater your grandma knit for you that you’ll
        hide until you need to wear it to a family event next December. We’ll do the hard work of
        remembering so that you don’t have to.\n
        \nHere’s how to use the main features of this app:\n</string>
    <string name="about_store_function">STORE\n\n
        If you tap this icon on the home screen or the plus sign on the search screen, it will take
        you to an input screen where you can store an item’s location. Here, you can type in the
        name of the item, put it in a category for easier finding later, and use one of two options
        to indicate its actual storage location. You can type in that the “Shirt” is in the “Dresser”
        or you can take a picture of the item where you plan on keeping it. Just tap on the icon
        corresponding to your choice of input, and then you can press the ‘Add’ button to store the
        item’s information in the app’s file directory.\n</string>
    <string name="about_search_function">SEARCH\n\n
        Once you’ve entered an item or two, when you need to remember where you hid
        grandma’s sweater, you can tap on this icon on the home screen to go to a screen that lists
        all the items you have stored. These can be viewed either in alphabetical order or by
        category, and you can switch between these views by tapping the three dots on the right side
        of the toolbar at the top of the screen. If you’re in a rush, you can also type an item’s
        name directly into the search field in the middle of the toolbar, and it should show up in
        the list view.\n </string>
</resources>